Akinrinola Muiz

Lagos, Nigeria | +234 7081386939 | akinrinolamuiz22@gmail.com | x.com/AkinrinolaMuiz

CAREER SUMMARY

I am a passionate frontend developer with over 1 years of experience in developing and implementing innovative software solutions. I am dedicated to delivering software solutions that drive business success. I am eager to learn and contribute my expertise to a forward-thinking organization that values innovation, teamwork, and continuous learning.

EDUCATION

Moshood Abiola Polytechnic

National Diploma in Computer Engineering

Tosef Model College

High School Diploma

Abeokuta, Nigeria

July, 2023

Lagos, Nigeria August, 2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Developer Intern

Zidio technology, India

India.

March 2024 - July 2024

- Collaborated with the product team to design application software
- Coded software updates and alterations based on detailed design specifications.
- Solved complex problems using the latest web technologies.

Java Programming Lang Student

Code-verse ltd, Nigeria

Abeokuta, Nigeria

Dec 2022 - March 2023

- Writing java code to implement software features and functionalities according to design and architecture
- Worked at an independent level, while also serving as an effective collaborator.
- Performed data entry tasks with accuracy and speed unitizing Java programs and IDE's.

Graphics Designer

Lagos, Nigeria

Anike Robert Clothing, Nigeria

Nov 2021 - Dec 2022

- Created flyers, and other marketing designs
- Utilized software such as Adobe xd, Photoshop, Microsoft word and excel.
- Created mockups and designs for clothing materials for branding and other printable materials/products

PROJECTS

- Built a robust web application using modern frameworks and technologies at Zidio internship training
- Developed an e-commerce website, using react and react hooks which is responsive and neat designs, and reuseable components.
- API Development: Created a RESTful API to facilitate data exchange between different software systems.
- Designed and developed a functional billing and result management system application, using java programming language and Mysql for the database

SKILLS

Technical Skills: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Sass, vite, React, Git, Firebase and UI/UX

Soft Skills: Clear communication skills, strong leadership skills, wonderful customer service, good pressure management, team player.

Fun Activities: Reading, Music lover, Movies, Coding and Sleeping.

TRAINING AND CERTIFICATIONS

- https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/image/UC-7b63b3c6-d1a2-44f4-b432-9c1aee06766e.jpg
- https://github.com/MuizAyomide

REFEREE

Available on request.